<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Northern Signals</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Northern Signals</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 21:48:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Five New Technologies I Used And Liked In 2018</title>
      <link>/2017/12/30/five-new-technologies-i-used-and-liked-in-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/12/30/five-new-technologies-i-used-and-liked-in-2018/</guid>
      <description>1. Pi-Hole This is my top pick for 2018 for very practical reasons. The Pi-Hole project identifies the domain names of ads from your DNS requests and points them to an un recoverable ip (a black hole). This allows you to have the best ad free experience online available without any configuration of the devices on your local network besides adding it as your own DNS service on the router. There are still ads on domains that serve their own ads (google, facebook, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An overview of public transit feeds around the world</title>
      <link>/2017/05/05/an-overview-of-public-transit-feeds-around-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/05/an-overview-of-public-transit-feeds-around-the-world/</guid>
      <description>The gtfs and gtfs-realtime are the modern standards for sharing public transit scheduled data and current updates to routes. The embedded script will tell you what is currently publicly shared (transitfeeds.com) and what is currently being published to google.
As of the writing of this script, there are 96 different realtime feeds from a handful of agencies around the world that publish an updated, and available publicly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>There are actually very few public, realtime gtfs feeds</title>
      <link>/2017/05/05/there-are-actually-very-few-public-realtime-gtfs-feeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2017 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/05/there-are-actually-very-few-public-realtime-gtfs-feeds/</guid>
      <description>Using the script from an earlier post, An overview of public transit feeds around the world, I organized and cleaned up the public realtime feeds available at transitfeeds.com. The number I came up with in the earlier post for number of agency feeds is actually smaller! Many agencies have seperated their alert, positions, and trip update feeds. Wow, so it actually much smaller,
library(RCurl) # grab a csv online throgh https github_csv &amp;lt;- getURL(&amp;quot;https://raw.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>